(Penny:)...but the truth is
you are just pathetic and creepy.
(Howard:)Um...
(Howard:)So, what are you saying?
(Penny:)I am saying it is not a compliment
to call me doable.
It is not sexy to stare at my ass
and say:
[AS HOWARD] "Ooh, it must be jelly,
because jam don't shake like that."
[IN NORMAL VOICE] Most important,
we are not dancing a tango.
We're not to-ing and fro-ing.
Nothing is ever gonna happen
between us. Ever.
(Howard:)Wait a minute. This isn't flirting.
You're serious.
(Penny:)Flirting? You think I'm flirting with you?
I am not flirting with you.
(Penny:)No woman is ever gonna flirt with you.
You're just gonna grow old and die alone.
(Howard:)Thanks for the heads up.
- Howard, where are you going?
- I'm going home...
(Howard:)...to live my creepy, pathetic life.
(Leonard:)Wow.
Well, y... Someone had to say it.